(node:25316) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/gwara/furvise-runner-live-memory-1/repair-live-memory-management/worktree/app/lib/intelligence/memory-integrity.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\gwara\furvise-runner-live-memory-1\repair-live-memory-management\worktree\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ actual loaders reject foreign owner/pet and inactive rows (50.489ms)
✔ actual profile loader rejects returned foreign profile (7.7188ms)
✔ legacy forget retains marker and POST suppresses normalized forgotten text (20.4578ms)
✔ POST stored replay cannot advertise a forgotten detail as saved (11.7445ms)
✔ actual legacy card Forget dispatches a source-aware DELETE (19.5187ms)
✔ old callback after pet switch cannot write a memory (9.7079ms)
✔ POST blocks existing rejected text without deleting or inserting (7.1731ms)
✔ POST blocks existing superseded text without deleting or inserting (9.6064ms)
✔ POST allows eligible distinct text and suppresses duplicates within request (6.672ms)
✔ forget is owner/pet scoped, repeatable, and retains other rows (7.4432ms)
✔ POST fails safely on storage failure (6.9714ms)
✔ DELETE fails safely on storage failure (5.6555ms)
✔ POST unique-conflict recovery excludes inactive, foreign-owner and other-pet rows (5.4506ms)
✔ stored POST replay fails closed when current rows cannot be verified (7.0317ms)
✔ old initial load resolving after switch never supplies new pet details (8.5063ms)
✔ in-flight refresh after pet switch cannot replace new pet rows (7.1861ms)
✔ canonical and legacy colliding IDs keep distinct routes; legacy edit/confirm and unknown IDs are rejected (10.9327ms)
✔ actual wrapper keys change with pet and data version; version refresh starts empty (6.601ms)
✔ actual loaders reject expired, malformed-scope and machine rows but retain valid global owner preferences (3.7096ms)
✔ unchanged actual canonical confirm delegates to lifecycle authority (4.895ms)
✔ unchanged actual canonical edit delegates to lifecycle authority (4.8833ms)
✔ unchanged actual canonical forget delegates to lifecycle authority (4.095ms)
✔ unchanged canonical route rejects foreign memory and ineligible correction without RPC (10.937ms)
✔ actual optional compatibility loader rejects foreign owner/pet and inactive rows (4.2803ms)
✔ pet switching while session lookup awaits prevents dispatch (6.6411ms)
✔ POST fails closed for unavailable or truncated suppression inventory: null (4.9367ms)
✔ POST fails closed for unavailable or truncated suppression inventory: 2 (4.4551ms)
ℹ tests 27
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 27
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 474.8658
